(Returning Pearl)
(اللؤلؤة العائدة)
Assassin!
قاتل!
She's not the real princess!
إنها ليست الأميرة الحقيقية!
- Here it comes, the iconic scene of "My Fair Princess"! - Stop her!
- ها هو المشهد الأيقوني من فيلم "أميرتي الجميلة" قادم! - أوقفوها!
- What are you doing? - Zi Wei!
- ماذا تفعل؟ - زي وي!
Yes! It's Zi Wei!
نعم! إنه زي وي!
Er Kang, there seems to be some disturbance at the rear.
إر كانغ، يبدو أن هناك بعض الاضطرابات في الخلف.
Go check it out.
اذهب للتحقق من ذلك.
I'll hold things here. This could be a diversion.
سأحتفظ بالأشياء هنا. قد يكون هذا تشتيتًا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let go of me!
أتركني!
Xiao Yan Zi, if you're the princess, then who am I?
شياو يان زي، إذا كنتِ الأميرة، فمن أنا؟
Who am I?
من انا؟
Beat her up!
اضربها!
Your Majesty...
جلالتك...
Er Kang! Er Kang, turn around!
إر كانغ! إر كانغ، يستدير!
That's Zi Wei! Your Zi Wei!
هذا زي وي! زي وي خاصتك!
Turn around and look at her!
التفت وانظر إليها!
Your Majesty!
جلالتك!
Stop! Stop it!
توقف! توقف!
She's just a defenseless girl.
إنها مجرد فتاة عاجزة.
Won't you at least hear her out?
ألا يمكنك على الأقل أن تستمع إليها؟
Is this any way to treat someone?
هل هذه طريقة لمعاملة شخص ما؟
Looks like you're in this together.
يبدو أنكما في هذا معًا.
Keep hitting her!
استمر بضربها!
Come on!
تعال!
Let go of me! Go away!
دعني أذهب! اذهب بعيدا!
Why did you act so recklessly?
لماذا تصرفت بتهور؟
My lord...
سيدي...
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
(Key plot point achieved. New character unlocked.)
(تم تحقيق نقطة الحبكة الرئيسية. تم فتح شخصية جديدة.)
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Where is that girl?
أين تلك الفتاة؟
Where is she?
أين هي؟
Have some water first.
اشرب بعض الماء أولاً.
That girl has been taken away by Lord Fu.
لقد تم أخذ تلك الفتاة من قبل اللورد فو.
You, on the other hand,
أنت، من ناحية أخرى،
you risked your life to save her.
لقد خاطرت بحياتك لإنقاذها.
What is your connection to her?
ما هي علاقتك بها؟
She...
هي...
She's my childhood friend.
إنها صديقة طفولتي.
Childhood friend?
صديق الطفولة؟
After all these years apart,
بعد كل هذه السنوات المنفصلة،
how can you be so sure?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون متأكداً هكذا؟
While that girl may seem vulnerable,
في حين أن تلك الفتاة قد تبدو ضعيفة،
how could you be sure she wasn't working with others?
كيف يمكنك التأكد من أنها لم تكن تعمل مع الآخرين؟
Causing a commotion here as a distraction,
التسبب في ضجة هنا كنوع من التشتيت،
while her accomplices tried to attack the princess?
بينما حاول شركاؤها الاعتداء على الأميرة؟
No, she wouldn't.
لا، لن تفعل ذلك.
I trust her.
انا اثق بها.
She's still the same Zi Wei I knew.
إنها لا تزال نفس زي وي التي أعرفها.
Gentle on the outside,
لطيف من الخارج،
but brave at heart.
ولكن شجاع في القلب.
Seeing her again,
رؤيتها مرة أخرى،
she's even braver than before.
لقد أصبحت أكثر شجاعة من ذي قبل.
You look
انت تبدو
different today.
مختلفة اليوم.
What was I like before?
كيف كنت من قبل؟
You were selfish.
لقد كنت أنانيًا.
Always lying.
الكذب دائما
You also look different today.
أنت تبدو مختلفًا اليوم أيضًا.
How so?
كيف ذلك؟
I never thought the Living King of Hell from the Department of Punishments
لم أكن أعتقد أبدًا أن الملك الحي للجحيم من إدارة العقوبات
had a heart for playing the hero.
كان لديه قلب للعب دور البطل.
Thank you, Lord Jing.
شكرا لك يا سيد جينغ.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Lin Er, come here!
لين إير، تعالي هنا!
Is it true you saved a girl from the common folk today?
هل صحيح أنك أنقذت فتاة من عامة الناس اليوم؟
That wasn't me, it was Lord Fu who saved her.
لم يكن أنا، بل كان اللورد فو الذي أنقذها.
Tell me, what did she look like?
أخبرني كيف كان شكلها؟
She's as lovely as a painting,
إنها جميلة مثل اللوحة،
but she's braver than she looks.
لكنها أكثر شجاعة مما تبدو عليه.
Oh, right,
اوه صحيح
she told me
لقد قالت لي
her name was Zi Wei.
وكان اسمها زي وي.
It really is Zi Wei!
إنه حقا زي وي!
She's actually...
إنها في الواقع...
I can't tell you!
لا أستطيع أن أخبرك!
Lin Er, since she's staying with Lord Fu now,
لين إير، بما أنها تقيم مع اللورد فو الآن،
how can I meet her?
كيف يمكنني مقابلتها؟
Xiao Yan Zi,
شياو يان زي,
if she can't come into the palace,
إذا لم تتمكن من دخول القصر،
you can go out to see her.
يمكنك الخروج لرؤيتها.
But leaving the palace isn't easy.
لكن مغادرة القصر ليس بالأمر السهل.
Come on, you're Xiao Yan Zi!
هيا، أنت شياو يان زي!
With your skills,
مع مهاراتك،
hopping over a wall or two should be a piece of cake!
القفز فوق جدار أو جدارين يجب أن يكون قطعة من الكعكة!
That's true!
هذا صحيح!
(The Art of War)
(فن الحرب)
What is this thing called love...
ما هذا الشيء الذي يسمى الحب...
That it makes one pledge life itself?
أنها تجعل الإنسان يتعهد بالحياة نفسها؟
You're writing
أنت تكتب
my name?
اسمي؟
But what does it mean?
ولكن ماذا يعني ذلك؟
Year after year of safety.
سنة بعد سنة من الأمان.
Year after year of safety?
سنة بعد سنة من الأمان؟
They're simplified characters.
إنهم شخصيات مبسطة.
Simplified characters?
حروف مبسطة؟
Anyway,
على أي حال،
you really do need to practice your handwriting.
أنت حقا بحاجة إلى ممارسة خط يدك.
Your writing and the Princess's are
كتاباتك وكتابات الأميرة
equally atrocious.
فظيعة بنفس القدر.
What do you know?
ماذا تعرف؟
This is a To-sign.
هذه علامة "إلى".
Do you have any idea how many people want
هل لديك أي فكرة عن عدد الأشخاص الذين يريدون
an exclusive signature from a big star like me?
توقيع حصري من نجم كبير مثلي؟
- Talking nonsense again. - You have the nerve to call it ugly!
- تتحدث هراء مرة أخرى. - لديك الجرأة لتسميها قبيحة!
Forget it. I'm not writing anymore. I'm not giving it to you.
انسَ الأمر. لن أكتب لك بعد الآن. لن أعطيك إياه.
Alright, alright.
حسناً حسناً.
If your writing's bad, then practice more.
إذا كانت كتابتك سيئة، فتدرب أكثر.
Hard work makes up for lack of talent.
العمل الجاد يعوض عن الافتقار إلى الموهبة.
Tell me what you want to write.
أخبرني ماذا تريد أن تكتب.
I'll teach you.
سأعلمك.
I want to write...
أريد أن أكتب...
What is this thing called love...
ما هذا الشيء الذي يسمى الحب...
Got him flustered, didn't I?
لقد أربكته، أليس كذلك؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Lord Jing, don't tell me you don't know this poem?
يا سيد جينغ، لا تخبرني أنك لا تعرف هذه القصيدة؟
That's not difficult.
هذا ليس صعبا.
Tell me the strokes of your simplified characters.
أخبرني عن ضربات شخصياتك المبسطة.
I will write them for you.
سأكتبها لك.
The first stroke
الضربة الأولى
is a dot.
هي نقطة.
Focus.
ركز.
It's so stuffy in here.
إنه خانق جدًا هنا.
I need some fresh air.
أحتاج إلى بعض الهواء النقي.
(What is this thing called love, that it makes one pledge life itself?)
(ما هو هذا الشيء الذي يسمى الحب، الذي يجعل الإنسان يتعهد بالحياة نفسها؟)
Xiao Yan Zi just left.
شياو يان زي غادر للتو.
I need to keep an eye on that Living King of Hell.
أحتاج إلى مراقبة ذلك الملك الحي للجحيم.
Can't let him ruin the crucial reunion between the sisters.
لا يمكن أن تسمح له بتدمير اللقاء الحاسم بين الأختين.
Weird.
غريب.
Why is nobody here?
لماذا لا يوجد أحد هنا؟
Oh no. Has our plan been exposed?
أوه لا، هل انكشفت خطتنا؟
Sneaking into my room in the dead of night,
تسلل إلى غرفتي في منتصف الليل،
what are you plotting?
ماذا تخطط له؟
What could I possibly be plotting?
ما الذي من الممكن أن أخطط له؟
How can a woman like you behave so shamelessly?
كيف يمكن لامرأة مثلك أن تتصرف بلا خجل؟
I need to buy Xiao Yan Zi more time.
أحتاج إلى شراء شياو يان زي المزيد من الوقت.
What's a big man like you so shy about?
ما الذي يخجل منه رجل كبير مثلك؟
Let me have one look, it's not like you'll suffer any losses.
دعني ألقي نظرة واحدة، ليس الأمر وكأنك ستعاني من أي خسائر.
Just one look!
نظرة واحدة فقط!
Let go. Let go!
دعها تذهب. دعها تذهب!
How is this robe so easy to tear?
كيف يمكن لهذا الثوب أن يتمزق بسهولة؟
Well, the plot is progressing very conveniently.
حسنًا، تتقدم القصة بشكل مريح للغاية.
I like it.
أحبها.
Don't go too far!
لا تذهب بعيدا جدا!
Her Majesty has arrived!
لقد وصلت جلالتها!
I'm doomed.
لقد حُكم علي بالهلاك.